I welcome back to our wheel of life
online retreat bring it
the proper law is known as online and
edited colors arena and we've reached
our third session it wasn't a Stigliano
I apologize that the meditation in the
second section went on too long
such a pressure machine estimated at
softer ominous Dennis from La Jolla
Slifkin Doga let's try to sell it I
registered the vegetable problem and the
Tristana lead timer so there's a
tradition when you teach the steps to
the path he talks wishes to etiquette I
did such to cook down but I need a
shaggy no poutine that you try to
connect this whole retreat to the last
retreated Rupa Titus said in Indonesia
that reads resolution so first session
three online session three in that long
line satiate three we're gonna review
where we left off in the last retreat
modest multimedia must analyse not as
lady Middleton I think it was in Bali
with many friends there the numerous
Toyota below non-violence undocumented
Regina so we you know we're studying the
medium person's motivation that means
the Chairman about so saying in
statistics coverage Shaka they want to
get out of all trouble life and you had
that these buyers are definitely
atmosphere isn't it
they want to reach nirvana and you have
this ditch near Ivana by the way it
doesn't mean they want to disappear
start anything is not just on you I
thought the ship just their life becomes
perfect things II know it's a selling
and they don't have a single problem in
this life you and you can get me
annoying problemo that's like Guinea out
of the jail most of a good sense to me
but there's a famous joke in the steps
to the task mummy where's Natasha
Ganapathy aluminum if you don't know
you're in the jail you don't want to get
out of the chip yes the green is night
están ahora tested Mia over
it is new Bratva so we will we have to
talk about why are we in the Junior I
don't but you move my to the Mia and
we've reached the part in the long room
where we talk about dying when they
stick the dough chest tell him I can't
go anymore my right knee which is kind
of like going from one cell in the jail
to the other cell in the jail the
personal pity what is that no candidate
to me after me after work I'm out of
touch email
but if you understand how each cell door
works nothing open your minds a cock
reported car that did come in your
camera then you can break out of the
jail that was motor to implead what they
still talk about you know how do people
die I don't wanna let him at on
calculator out and what happens is the
bracelet cut down and we've reached a
very important part of the death process
humanistic the ocean bars my chest
processes Mirta which is called Santa
Catarina's odds are soon peppa and I'm
gonna in these alarming teachings
inventor Puccini a columbarium
I'm gonna sprinkle in some Tibetan and
Sanskrit words
yes average the by depravity very
traditional Chinese word and I think
it's gonna make your experience deeper
he had emerged on Tisdale in Foshan for
the blueprint so please don't be afraid
of the foreign words but more but almost
in your pocket a sinister explore every
word you learn will increase your
knowledge
Garnett's lolcat arrival bootchie bootch
it will be leech it washes Mannie and
that will increase your ability to break
out of the jail until deletion washes
personas a little says German so here's
the Tibetan I'll pronounce it is that
what to be Itsuki opinion so soon debut
near Lake anima Minami
so when you're about to die Dada
there's like a lottery that goes on in
your mind watching on airplanes when
they start of a credulity so in your
brain Russian mafia there are many many
many seeds used monogamy no national
that you collected during your lifetime
Keturah with psoriasis or in summer good
seats negative Hiroshi Shima not summer
bad secretary policeman on and actually
there are millions of doses in a song
they make me no one now just that the
crucial moment of death of the rough
state of mind in death across Cretaceous
key moment smear to vote advantage also
stay in your mouth Melton your mind
takes one of those Karma's out of
millions gosh they don't admit million
of it when it picks it it's kind of like
it turns on the timer for a pop you can
download right on kind of catch
antimatter lebombo so you saw those hero
movies and that respond trilogy feel
mind you know we're like 10 long are
Thank You Olivia come the bad guy sets a
nuclear bomb law-abiding just
annihilated an unborn ball he turns on a
timer on Concetta timer and maybe it's a
60-minute time more too much attached
STDs team and not nighttime and the good
hero has 60 minutes to stop the bomb you
have a growing issue this has been
noticed of a stone and it's bomba
so that timer is actually a smaller
attack a depend on the sound a lineage a
bomba and when the time runs out you
know hey mister Guyot the smaller bomb
goes off and it it triggers the bigger
boom boom enchiladas menaced Roboto it
is a prescribed
oh boy wise man sir in Tibet in the word
soon depa attack materials come with a
slower song depa mean sir to put on the
timer as an Excel spreadsheet time and
that that will cause the bomb to enter
sister Land Boom Boom's are lotsa and in
this case the bomb is your next life
even time solution and a bomb by the
translator generation so just as you are
dying attack at all common right they
turn on the seeds in your mind possum
says my name click Share to cement timer
timer and in that seed will blow up you
take that at the same a provider and it
will push you into the next life anta
told no it was later sharing so it's
very important to choose the right seat
to be watching fires now we brought
private nation or not and there is a way
there's a system about this is Gemma
injection on and that was the last thing
we studied in the lamrim involved in
developing later story as a challenge
not long but he never pilot last time
would you come here problem we talked
about who decide what's it is gonna be
selected in the lottery window Eli Tomac
door - I had casino budget would run a
lottery and in this learning book we had
three decision romantic ninja on women
as his traditional first one era
Leacock top shower means LeCompte oh
yeah who decides which seed will open a
dozen check toward a shot across a mat
currents theorem well we see this more
power Tecna has done approach Cena she
named you know like a powerful birthday
would be like you killed somebody no
matter what the commotion apply Jose
meant a toast of a coatl be more
powerful good CD save someone's life
one time in your
in emotional hiroshi same a thirst of a
comment especially she's not not them
and I have said the person's life and
it's the greatest feeling he yeah not
the visually equator
silica definition every wooden canoe
supposed principal attack Caribbean what
was the most powerful see I can Shana
below some obscene okay
second to spiff Terrapins opinion can
combo Jana Jana can if the power of the
two states is equal yes the Sheila the
book Shima nom nom which one will open
what groans appear on and I don't know
let's say you you lied to you told a big
lie in your life and I'm the poster boy
she knows all right but you also
criticize someone very badly in your
life I'm a type of shop which is in the
critical I like about them change now
and chemically to tell a big lie and to
give a big criticism somebody you can
meet you scared cuz I but sure logical
what I've seen not as critical but those
two comments are almost equal
ancient register practice care only so
which one will open first required
courage appear on it can't open at the
same thing anymore top concern of
America Russia one has to open first
another's not crates of pyramid and he
says combat Sheva means uncover it works
for sure are you more used to doing
Kakui lavas boy Larry which now like are
you a person who who likes to lie all
the time to people we took a tour a
little bit of Serrano God don't give new
them are you angry person who criticizes
other people it was Lloyd Chile Ecuador
a little bit more time comes for those
two states to open lying and criticizing
the junk of the pyramid creeps into
aluminum really create again then which
one you did more often as a habit in
your questioning with Yoli ChaCha Capri
which cost version
that seed will be selected at the moment
of death the same amudha lubrano mine
and smelter okay and then then the Texas
Jaime Amla and the champion good chin
youngnam can Amla Chapa quite good the
biscuits or nuts doing this if supposed
to have that propel awesome story which
kid only it's supposed to power the
Karma's equally power to heal it a karma
or not well then which one did you do
first understood this deal theorem which
one came before the other this table
round rock or teeny last cent depth of
that one will be selected any loss and
episode he IDI booted WebRunner now
there's a very very very very very very
famous book about emptiness watching
ocean ocean ocean is via technical
process which is called gumbo dr. Thomas
Watson bar up so which means I will
illuminate for you
what chant the Quixote and the garden
are really meant about emptiness does
not shed in a person she was Chandra
Quixote in The Guardian meditation not
immediately do cognitive area pasta and
that book is by second an abyss man
chats on copy and I I think it's maybe
the greatest book here you had immersed
or was more tinnitus on my villa
Technotronic Italian himself and he has
the same question Young's out of Dodge
of across which which karma will be
selected which timer will be set okay
Carmen budget will connect a great army
time I put it Estonian and he gets a
little bit more detailed explanation
tell him another bullet Petrovna Mishnah
and that comes from an arbiter METEC yet
applies hold this text I be Dharma Abbot
Dharma is some of
the most ancient teachings of Buddhism
in this world I mean our meta ignore is
somewhat iyanya with changing would use
my baton meter very difficult wishing
throat man stan is actually translating
the most famous book stand in the sound
deliberative what did someone just
knocking ago he's scheduled to finish in
2046 on dozens of quantitative data
structures Tonga do
and in that book never taken India
there's a poem is to Iranian and it's
supposed to be by the Buddha polygons
are stunning presentation of Buddha and
I wanted to give that to you and and I
will do that during these long room
teaches yeah I tell that I'm evolved to
Cheney at Cheney aluminum on if I think
some idea is very important you say I
don't wash to occur at idea what she was
not like which open first what I died
vacation and not courts okay woodcutter
they don't rule to me that's a very
important question
eliminate the ocean of ours no across so
sometimes I will go deeper on a question
from another book in Adana
Yahoo bless for us is through work in
deep IMO and that's why this
retwist takes a lot of my territory
doesn't happen over Damon vanishes right
now so I'd like to take this poem from
Vassar ponder and from Buddha document
album shared to the state Vanina what
was a bundle in yet would Lake ecologic
on Danielle Condon comic con mucho
Caliente Dalai Lama hominem engine is
the poem what a stack of arena Leakey
Karachi condom ladies oMG Canton means
when the karma makes you spin in the we
on chattering the caramel ganache diet
was rushed shots of calcium there's a
certain priority system mr. Brennan
assistant planet yet some seeds have to
open before others negative Nando's not
as carboxyl institutional and that
depends on certain factors yet as a
visit at the Britain on the vodka chakal
means well which commerce is more
serious
she can't as Michelle Carmen bullish
Arianna like killing someone is is more
serious than line will be vodka what a
bullet in your national guard Komodo
then it says new account that don't go
edit New York on which one is closer ok
questioning beliefs and this is a very
very important idea yet I wish she
notion Barton idea which we'll talk more
about in in future segments of this
lahrman a Qatari bhagavad Romney I'm
scared shake shake mentor at the Valois
Murray mom but closer means closer to
the moment of leisure as much AdBlue
sacramento's me actor so certain kinds
of seeds certain kinds of karma that
I've really only listen on a pretty long
name with the Karma even though maybe
they are not as serious as other cars
Dashon is Mitrano touched on you need
oxygen ecology if you do them closer to
the moment of your death and and passing
on New Year's Day with society who blue
Sacramento washes Mirta is a gentleman
writer then they will take parity and
empower child predator like if you have
a great desire on the last day of you
know know primera is the was his caucus
transnational line of a slain Indiana
versus reasoning it can change which
karma timer is put on on motion as me
talk a quicker me to skate I'm a clue
cheetah and we'll talk in a polka very
mom bottom then it says combatant which
one did you do more frequently or later
discovered it's a combatant Kaku is new
agility polish asta which one did you
get used to because used to do a lot the
term of a pre weekly paddle most of
chastity autumn and you know one thing I
don't like about this online class yes
of knowledge Catania reservation land
Plaza I like to Chris my students and
and offer reward money
UNITA process to gentlemen
and we met wasn't gardenia so this I
don't get to do it in the online name
ago does the online class so this class
gonna be cheaper for me next act as an
anti Buddha dis chevrolet lumina but
it's fun for me to do that kind of
gambling union rights as in you Martha
what a special stand it so here it says
combi that was this good it's a combi
and it's pronounced combi yet apprentice
a coma yeah and it means you got used to
something yet as a chat degree with
tomahto you gotta have with your HP
vertica then there's another Tibetan
word Tommy HT shown that the viscous
losses from Dolores so all are you not
gonna get money only Stanley and Allison
will get money during this one next week
pollution it's a dinky Tonka Stanley
listen poacher danger Shane I think if
they don't get it correct they should
give me my scientist Brian I need
mineable dominant okay so if you change
the pronunciation I'm sure yes the way
is main surprise machinae combat means
to get used to home bar as much as
people schemata for $100 dollars Daniel
maybe we can have him represent someone
in the audience more hunter which much
more some that evil or what appetizer
like gumbo
doesn't share the global global Goomba
Goomba sounds almost the same we should
practice keep in touch I'll give you
just a dollar stop and throw me okay
that's very interesting again I was in
interest that the ancient word for
meditation area slower business and
shaming the table-saw comes from race
hoarded the word which means to do
something over and over until you get
used to it
in sloka thought I wasn't Chad you're
just totally bust no waste no I forgot
Academy privilege and the idea for
example in the seven part meditation
preparation which we did in the last
thing he didn't know primera for me to
talk say see me she's she's taken to
Ramadan of purslane and video if you
appreciate and express your gratitude to
your teacher over and over in the
meditation just if it changes I want you
to leverage ayat Emoto block of darkness
no ways no I mean did dad say then that
will become a habit
anyway no tree which come and your mind
will change the Russian ones mean itself
and you will become a person who is more
grateful to other people I was telling
ttme i come cut or avoided bully blog
and Armando Kim okay now the other
factor that gossip on dimensions in the
ancient epidermis teaching Irish ensured
in fact purgatory was a bundle by
Menards and Rihanna mu Cheney abhidharma
one shake is also a factors which seat
did you play it before the other one
time center factor kakora scene of a
person is a ranch in the war now I spent
many you know I spent years working
through this explanation of three
factors that cause let's see to open
first and four factors the costs to open
first because we want to be sure to make
a good seed open first when we die yep
revenue order about an undetermined
beast neum Joe factor cut Roosevelt
creates a mini pyramidal factor cattle
was voted criticism in appear on but a
Muslim of hidimba to be a nurse the
Maharaja seem out crispy I don't cook
them home bro
so if you if you really studied this
quotation of system industry generates a
chat engine stop it in my opinion you
have to read it this way among clad
without Nick watch TED talk okay here we
go four factors she didn't factor which
decide Turin shard which Karma's can
open first in when a darker karma trots
Erica WHL okay then first rule are
getting Adira parabola generally
speaking no variable salons
some Pru
generally speaking the
seed that you planted first will open
first first-in first-out in accounting
system without Salim is a matter of a
pasadenian not be alone yet culture yet
of what had been overcome Bugatti
species team and that kind of makes
sense yeah this reason I mean it's
myself so I always remember this big lie
I did yes comes from an admin but she'll
or scatter oh yes Kazakh double rebuild
come only once in my whole life I stole
money he entrusted me okra okra Dean
gives away from my my mama
I still fight dr. pentola when I was
young and so let's say later when I was
in the diamond business cash imported
evolved a Muslim business business
separate powers me animals I wasn't
understand my taxes although I was a
Polish amiable chased and swimming no
longer make a terrible masala jelly so
let's say theoretically I cheated on
Jerry dish skia a journey chose Morgana
so it makes sense at the time of my
death attack a demeans missile of
momentum I smear time if those two seeds
haven't opened yet
it's letter device a munition your
clinic a quad-core yeah the first one I
do as a Crown Victoria so those shop WT
Blanca so that makes sense that I meant
missile first in first year we were show
p evolution no second factor to be a
power factor and and I'm interpreting
this to could be interpreted it to get
the data let's say in my diamond career
for 19 years
supposed to my arm as my career as I did
it not settling it I cheated on my taxes
every year yeah German Joseph a
monologue amigas the growth team times
did not surprise covered my home 19-year
career which it did not he atopic Rio
Summer did not stay late new career or
stone asam delayed
so you have one lie to my mom when I was
a kid
what the Nazis lost my anaconda yam
believe don't come then you have her
cheating on my taxes over and over which
takes about six months preparation you
shall join just one analog of cataract
artists in multiple would have to change
if not still yet and if those seats
karmas didn't open years lattissima na
karma near a screen is a shocker
mementos have died which will be
triggered and Rockaway sneakers cards
appear on yeah nineteen years of
Chileans is not simply a just Winchester
even though it came after the lie when I
was a kid davin is Montana
Thurston operational Bosnia wrinkle
devil him beyond come the third factor
beta factor what if I'm in the hospital
especially I've been in seong around and
I'm dying young around and don't forget
in Buddhism is a bunch of bodies man
dying is not really an SDF tetanus
oundle in the opinions my rough
consciousness dies my group west of
Miami right and then I go to a very very
primordial ancient consciousness subtle
consciousness in today Duke's alma
better on a chair I'm at on come on
Sonya so in the moment of that
transition of my mind my amputee who
wasn't my Obama from being aware of this
world artisans ninety-eight of amira to
the ancient ancient stream of mind which
I have had for billions of years
Manorama Lardon yet so in that delicate
moment of the last ability of my mind to
have a normal thought I don't bother us
lady Mamiya per semester my OMA mostly
not mine now what if in that moment my
family is crying and the grandma don't
go don't go don't mind semi applies it
applies at any hotel never when you
continue handy then my mind is almost
dying to a subtle but don't my much to
me right nighttime tone come now I can't
even recognize who's grabbing my arm and
that's a human would expose magic door
attack my little it's my kid or my wife
at mansion I'll my hip you wanna like I
feel this grab my arm and I choose to
worship them now what adds suddenly I
remember a fight I had when I was a
teenager in Tropius permanent rapid
ramen umbilical - abu pedroka
it's summer grandma taught us what young
as a rakuyo dialogue so in that subtle
meaning attacked by the donkey man meant
me not o when my mind is going from this
life mind back to my settlement Kadamba
wanted to stay I needed reasoning but at
my donkey wound in that moment someone
casma but at my milk told them what had
hatred that I choose to immunize
Katerina chose to all content across
come then that was gonna cancel the two
other ones yet academicians guys say
nothing that minions of a drug you
forget the lie when your kid is a booty
illogical down with a ribbon come forget
the cheating on your tax even though it
went on for 19 years of whatever
injustice no organized resettable of to
change it is not still yet in that
crucial moment whether - Irish money and
if you feel intense anger they would
choose to a chair
Meganium yes which well that you can
question asker itself Kotaro daily
partner and and we'll talk more about
the population boys on bottom but then
obviously it's very important that
people die in a very conducive peaceful
atmosphere no achieve in our store which
involves no stupid idiot owner I live
like a pretty at night me an atmosphere
yes then we have lamb sacred thing in
common we have to be careful here to
make sure they die in a peaceful way
those name it's a karate I'm Antonio was
aboard Saddam's - Vanina smear on her
shop okay the room should be combatted
hours not with Mira now the people
standing around I said that they are not
making loud frightening noises did you
get arrested for Okinawa cruising man no
enemies David groans poker chips Luca
okay no fourth one Hershiser pitched it
worked so so far we had some lie I did
when I was a smoke that they supported
us block of metal or shuttle yes Kazakh
government might even come in normally
that one should open first he a boots
not another's not creates a beer away at
death for example whatever smear Tintin
I know if I did a similar line but over
and over for 19 years yes the until
before she lost not to shame if it does
not sell it and that this karma will
come to the front of the line ahead of
the kid camera died at the Karma blatant
misogyny defeated token terrible him
welcome and that will decide where I go
in my next people that I would attend
shot go dad promise - yeah well no one
in the moment that was supposed to open
don't know me and cut down on Tom's
number of scribsy someone grab my total
mouse got a big anger she and now that
super
hot anger at the last moment we will
take priority
it's bill that goon of a slain elements
multiple widget worship planet yet
unless there was a very heavy coming yes
the dole commands reasonable voice
inches all the car you know like I went
to nineteen tacitly a portion of I know
I was struggling with another soldier
yesterday after him seldom and I
consciously point the gun at their head
and I yes has nothing on the proud
stallion in Israel that one is so much
more serious than lying to my mother
than 19 years of cheating my taxes Dan
someone grabbing my arm at nothing at
the garage got out the bullish the
Ornish am right my environment Jim did
not let you in shit analog mhm is like
total white another Ocampo slain element
like that at the Karma
Oh Beast Wow achieve in the budget we
arrived in a child this is the one that
makes sense to me how to read attack at
the door remains Muslim Limina capture
touch it pretty much it is to he stopped
until Dylan mobs or is a Conchie model
segment next time we're gonna practice
time its leadership dimension wouldn't
any robots on the right but not exactly
no disassemble
Brad generally speaking idea if if I did
it earlier I lie to my mom yesterday Oh
stutter on several same answer when I
was a cadet what a welcome generally
that one should open fingers manometer
doors not crits appear unless
yes natal later in my life portion for
my signal I did so Carol I for 19 years
do sort of Roger who safety change is
not still yet now that one should open
at the moment
dieter does not obscure it's on my man
smelter and this side where every delete
could die on a problem unless yes little
someone grabs
nothing is quite murder while I'm around
and suddenly I remember some violent
energy denying sponeck aquata Dean's
machine then that one will move to the
front about three minutes after you
torture them almost Oh Elka
yes left in my hole same arena I did
some very very serious bad deed like
killing and ezel Koda Oh is she
ocean surface topography beast weather
watcher echo so that's our review of the
where we stopped in the last which we
need a stash of terrain e&w must an
arena sniper selenium a treat and we're
ready to move on to segments and I'll
check video now HT no thank you and
thank you Stella fresh Eva Eva she
returned as a reward